Khaled Mohamed

khalied.mo2030@gmail.com

01019473809

linkedin.com/in/khaliedmuhamad

https://khali3d.netlify.app

Summary

I love to dig into problems and solve them with modern technology.

I enjoy learning about many executives throughout my career in engineering and Front-End Development. My personal and professional experiences have taught me the following about myself:

I educate, refine and drive myself to be a better person I am constantly learning because I never settle I stay calm when faced with adversity I focus on making high-quality decisions

I enjoy meeting new people and making friends.

I love applying responsive design principles and watching my web pages shrink into mobile screens and still look amazing. I think in a way I'm kind of like those web pages.

My specialties include quickly learning new skills and programming languages, responsive design principles, User Experience (UX), website optimization. So far I have JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, React, ¡Query, Bootstrap, d3.js, sass, pug, command line, and Git/GitHub under my belt. I've started learning Node.JS and Express.JS. I'm still enthusiastically grabbing onto any other programming languages, frameworks, or principles I can integrate into the coding web in my head.

I worked with slack and know about Agile Methodologies and Trello.

Experience



Coordinator

جمعية رسالة للأعمال الخيرية | Resala Charity Organization Sep 2021 - Present (8 months +)



Data Collector

ArgamFC

Apr 2021 - Present (1 year 1 month +)

football collector.

Specifing in-frame Player location during shots.



Video Coordinator

ArgamFC

Sep 2021 - Present (8 months +)

Responsible for providing soccer match videos.

feeding our database. making critical decisions.

Frontend Developer

Freelance

Jan 2020 - Aug 2021 (1 year 8 months)

- 1- Designing and developing several websites.
- 2- Creating responsive pages.
- 3- Creating landing pages.
- 4- Customizing and editing websites.
- 5- Making web applications with react.js.

Education

Banha university

Bachelor of Engineering , Mechanical Engineering 2020 - 2024

Licenses & Certifications

(A) Responsive Web Design - freeCodeCamp

fcc31eaef09-895c-4ee0-9cbf-cb34a5325400

- (A) JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures freeCodeCamp fcc31eaef09-895c-4ee0-9cbf-cb34a5325400
- (A) Front End Libraries freeCodeCamp
- **Front End Web Development Professional** Udacity

Skills

User Experience (UX) • Data Collection • Front-end Development • Web Development • Algorithms • Responsive Web Design • React Hooks • User Interface Design • Web Design • Strategic Planning